[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film The Graduate, Benjamin and Elaine make their escape using this type of transportation.", "correct_answer": "Bus", "incorrect_answers": ["Benjamins Alfa Romeo", "Helicopter", "Taxi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these waves have the highest wave length?", "correct_answer": "Radio waves", "incorrect_answers": ["Microwaves", "Infra -red  waves", "X-rays"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the basic chemical compound that natural pearls consist of?", "correct_answer": "Calcium carbonate", "incorrect_answers": ["Aluminum carbonate", "Sodium sulphate", "Calcium fluoride"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The word diamond comes from the ancient Greek word \u201cadamas\u201d meaning what translated in English?", "correct_answer": "Invincible", "incorrect_answers": ["Everlasting", "Powerful", "Brilliant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was drafted by the Orlando Magic as the 1st overall pick in the 1992 NBA draft?", "correct_answer": "Shaquille ONeal", "incorrect_answers": ["Christian Laettner", "Alonzo Mourning", "Anfernee Hardaway"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what city is the train station with the storage locker located in the movie Rat Race?", "correct_answer": "Silver City, NM", "incorrect_answers": ["Sun City, AZ", "Colorado City, AZ", "Santa Rosa, NM"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why so serious? is a tagline from this Batman movie.", "correct_answer": "The Dark Knight", "incorrect_answers": ["Batman Begins", "Batman Returns", "Batman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Hoosiers, Myra Fleener does not want Jimmy to play basketball.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the first President of the Russian Federation?", "correct_answer": "Boris Yeltsin", "incorrect_answers": ["Mikhail Kasyanov", "Viktor Khristenko", "Vladimir Putin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do the names Henry, Harry, Harrison, Hal, Hank, Enrique mean?", "correct_answer": "Home ruler", "incorrect_answers": ["Victorious warrior", "Active in battle", "Abundant land"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which number is the odd one out?", "correct_answer": "17462", "incorrect_answers": ["11780", "13491", "15183"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The U.S. Supreme Court ruled in 1972, that capital punishment was unconstitutional.  What was the name of the case?", "correct_answer": "Gregg v. Georgia", "incorrect_answers": ["Hammer v. Illinois", "Dagenhart v. Texas", "Furman  v. Florida"]}]